columbiacollege.bc.ca 2019-05-21

# Legal and Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy for Website Visitors 

#### Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information

When you register with Columbia College, we ask for information such as your name, organization information, email address, telephone number, and postal address. Columbia College will use the information gathered for the provision of services to you, including billing, authentication, contact, and registration.

#### Credit Card Information

Your transaction may be processed by a third-party payment vendor, Moneris or Flywire. These vendors are payment processors who can process your payment on behalf of Columbia College.

#### Protection of Personally Identifiable Information

Columbia College may disclose personally identifiable information to authorized employees and governmental agencies. Personal information will be managed by Columbia College in accordance with the British Columbia Personal Information and Protection Act. This will only be done on a need-to-know basis. Columbia College will take all reasonable measures to protect against unauthorized access, use, and alteration of personally identifying information. When passing personally identifying information to a third party, we will ensure that adequate protection of the information is applied by the recipient.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of information that websites can store on your computer. Your computer provides this cookie when visiting the same website in the future. Cookies are used to enhance your experience with a website. Visitors can disable the storage of cookies in their web browser, but should be aware that doing so may affect the quality of the experience with the website. In some cases, the website may not work at all.

#### Access to your Information

You can change any of the personally identifiable information volunteered to us by logging into the Columbia College [login area](https://webmail.columbiacollege.bc.ca/CookieAuth.dll?GetLogonWrapper?url=%2Fexchange&reason=0). If you would like us to delete any personally identifiable information held about you, we will do so on request unless we need to hold the information as part of the provision of services to you.

#### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, governmental agencies, and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) will have access to this information.

#### Contacting Columbia College

You may contact Columbia College using any of the methods outlined [here](https://www.columbiacollege.ca/about/contact-us).  
Our mailing address is:  
Columbia College  
438 Terminal Avenue  
Vancouver, BC  
V6A 0C1 Canada

#### Changes to this Policy

From time to time we may make adjustments to this privacy policy. Changes to this policy will be made at Columbia College’s sole discretion. Columbia College’s website users are encouraged to check this privacy policy for such changes. Your continued use of this site following changes to this privacy policy constitutes your acceptance of the changes.
